tynt.com 2015-03-17

# Privacy Policy | Tynt

Welcome to www.tynt.com (the “ **Site** ”), a website owned and controlled by Tynt Multimedia Inc. (“ **Tynt** ”, “ **we** ”, “ **us** ”, or “ **our** ”). We operate the Site, and Tynt software products and services made available through the Site (collectively the “Services”), which make link creation in copied and pasted content effortless to readers and, in certain cases, enables easier searches from copied content. We provide this privacy policy to let you know what information we collect, and how we use it, share it and protect it.

##  **Scope**

As a general rule, there are two categories of users of the Site and Services:

  * “ **Publishers** ” who are operators or publishers of websites that install the Services on their website(s) (collectively the “ **Publisher Sites** ”), and
  * “ **End Users** ” who are individual visitors of the Site and/or Publisher Sites.

This Privacy Policy applies to End Users of the Site and the End Users of Publisher Sites. By visiting the Site or Publisher Sites, you are accepting the policies and practices described in this Privacy Policy.

##  **Privacy Practices for Visitors to the Tynt Site**

(a) The information we gather and how we use it: The Site is primarily directed to Publishers, although we welcome End Users who want to know more about our Services. We do not collect any PII from End Users through the provision of our services. When a Publisher signs up for our site, we will collect the Publisher’s e-mail address to enable us to offer the service. A single e-mail address from the Publisher is the only Personally Identifiable Information (“ **PII** ”) that we collect and we do this only to enable login to the site and to enable us to contact the Publishers that use our Services.

(b) Controlling our use of Publisher Login Information: If you have provided your email address when registering for our Site, you may modify that information at any time by visiting your account settings (https://www.tynt.com/account/account_settings). You can also delete your account at any time. You can opt out of receiving certain email communications from the Site by clicking the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of each email.

(c) Information Sharing: We will use a Publisher email address provided at login exclusively as follows:

  * With third parties if we have a good faith belief that access, use, or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy applicable law, regulation, legal process or an enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce the applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Tynt, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.
  * In the event we go through a business transition such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, the Publisher’s email address may be among the assets transferred.

##  **Privacy Practices for End Users Who Visit Publisher Sites that have Tynt Services Installed**

We do not collect any PII from End Users who visit Publisher Sites.

We operate the Services, which make link creation in copied and pasted content effortless to readers and, in certain cases, which make searches from copied content easier. When you, an End User, copy content from a Publisher Site and paste it into another document, the Services that have been installed on the Publisher Site may, at the publishers discretion, automatically append a link back to the original content. When you visit a Publisher Site, we collect certain non-personally identifiable information (“Non-PII”) for use on our platform (the “Tynt Platform”). We enable our Publishers to use this information via the Platform for analytics purposes, and we also use some of this information to market our products and services to you and those of third parties we believe may be of interest to you as described below.

(a) The information we gather and how we use it:

  * **PII** – We do not collect PII from End Users who visit a Publisher Site.
  * **Non-PII** – We collect Non-PII through the provision of Services for use on the Tynt Platform. For example, when you visit a web page on a Publisher Site, our server logs may collect your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time you visited that web page, and the web search that landed you on that web page. We may also collect information regarding what content you copy from the Publisher Site. Also, when you visit a Publisher Site, we will place a cookie onto your computer or other device. “Cookies” are small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer’s web browser while you are viewing a website. We use cookies to improve the quality of our Services, including identifying user preferences and interests and identifying user trends. We also use cookies to help advertisers and publishers serve more relevant ads to users.

(b) Controlling our use of your Non-PII: If you don’t want us to (i) enable Tynt-generated links in connection with copied content, or (ii) track your Non-PII, you can opt-out by clicking the Opt Out button on this page. You will need to Opt-Out for each browser you use and have cookies enabled.

(c) Information Sharing: We share Non-PII with other companies or individuals as follows:

  * We use Non-PII to enable us to provide our Services to our Publisher partners. We also use Non-PII to enable advertisers to serve more relevant advertisements to their audience.
  * We share any information we have with third parties if we have a good faith belief that disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy applicable law, regulation, legal process or an enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce the applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Tynt, its End Users or the public as required or permitted by law.
  * In the event we go through a business transition such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, we expect that any and all information that we have will be among the assets transferred.
  * In addition, we may aggregate your Non-PII with the Non-PII of others and share that aggregated information with third parties without restriction.

##  **Information Security and Retention**

We take reasonable security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include firewalls and encryption, internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems.

We restrict access to Publisher email addresses to Tynt employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our Services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination, if they fail to meet these obligations. However, we are unable to guarantee that the security measures we take will not be penetrated or compromised or that your information will remain secure under all circumstances.

We retain records of Publisher email addresses for as long as the Publsher maintains its account.

We retain detailed records of End User activity for a maximum of 90 days. Statistical summaries and data aggregations may be kept for longer periods.

##  **Children**

We do not knowingly collect or maintain PII from any individuals – especially individuals who are under 13 years of age, and no part of our Site or Services are designed to attract people under the age of 13. Protecting the privacy of children is very important to us. If we obtain knowledge that a user is under the age of 13, we will take steps to remove that user’s data from our databases.

##  **Links to Other Sites**

Our Site and Services contain links to, and allow you to share content on, third party websites and services. The fact that we link to a website or service or allow you to share content on them is not an endorsement, authorization or representation that we are affiliated with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. This privacy policy applies only as provided in the “Scope” section above. Other websites and services follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of personal information. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

##  **International Users**

The Site and Services are hosted in the United States. If you access the Site or Services from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Site or Services, you are transferring your PII and non-PII to the United States (as we define non-PII in this Privacy Policy) and you consent to that transfer. Additionally, you understand that your PII may be processed in countries (including the United States) where laws regarding processing PII may be less stringent than in your country.

##  **Questions or Comments?**

Tynt regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy by contacting us through this Site, by emailing us at [privacy@33across.com](mailto:privacy@33across.com) or writing to us at:

33Across Inc.  
Attn: Privacy Officer  
229 West 28th Street,  
12th Fl  
New York, NY 10001

##  **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us any time through this Site or by writing to us at the address set forth above.

Last Updated: August 28, 2012
